<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Chiara Satta</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Chiara Satta</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
      <title>From Italy to the UK</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/beforetheuk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/beforetheuk/</guid>
      <description>Until 2015 I was born and bred in Sardinia. In 2015, I moved to the UK in Cambridge and after almost 10 years living here, I am now looking for my next adventure in Spain.
I have lived in Italy for most of my life. More than a decade ago, I graduated in Languages and Communication at the University of Cagliari and after spending some years as freelancer tutor of English in Italy, I decided to move to the UK to improve my English language skills but also to seek further professional opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Greeting! Welcome to my site.
In this section, you can find more information about my career and life before and after moving to the UK. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our British adventure</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/britishadventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/britishadventure/</guid>
      <description>2015 In 2015, I moved to Cambridge with Salvatore, my husband.
We jumped on the British adventure with two luggages each, no job offer and only five days of bed &amp;amp; breakfast booked.
After the first few weeks adjusting to the cold and damp, I found a volunteering opportunity in the bookshop of the Royal Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals – RSPCA - the largest animal welfare charity in the UK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working for Cambridge University</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/myexperienceatcambridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/myexperienceatcambridge/</guid>
      <description>2020 until now In February 2020, I got a job as an Insight Analyst in the Customer Insight team at Cambridge University Press &amp;amp; Assessment, English - part of the University of Cambridge. For two months right before the pandemic started, I worked in this fast-paced team doing sentiment and text analysis on customer survey material to build one of the largest customer experience database in the whole organisation.
But as my goal was still working in comms, at the same time as this job, I had applied for a role of Communication Coordinator in the PR team in the same department and got the role in April.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
